[{"answer": "Your pictures are all in the computer. Nobody keeps photo albums like this anymore, they're ancient relics. They should. I like being able to touch something, instead of it floating around in cyber world. If the laptop breaks, your whole existence is erased. 6", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You are a little kid", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What do you mean", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No I wasn't", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You were snoring", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yes you were", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes you were", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yes you do", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I don't snore", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "My father snored. I do not snore", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yes you do", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "How would you know what you do? You're asleep", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I respect your right to believe that, my friend. But I want to give you all possible theories. I want this class to go out into the world with an informed opinion", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "How can it be incorrect? It's a theory. A scientific theory", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend, where's the box of my lamps", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yeah, I packed them. They're not here. 15", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I didn't even notice", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "It's normal to want your own time", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I saw somebody", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No. It wasn't a shadow, it was a man. He was tall, and he long, greasy hair. He was wearing a grey jacket. He looked right at me", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Uh...what", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Just take it without me. 32", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "There's no one here", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I believe you, okay? I just don't know what you want me to do. 39", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I didn't know what else to do", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No. It was mine", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Do either of you habitually use drugs or alcohol", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No drugs at all", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I take ant", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Not a history. I've had bouts of it. In the past", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Mrs. my friend", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Last saw me", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "  They're very good assistants but I can't get them to dress any better", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Pleased to meet you. I'm my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "She tells me what she sees and I draw it. It's the most important part of her process", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Especially the drawings", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Especially the drawings", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "It's not debatable", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " They work together, so desperate are they to possess my friend. They are the closest of all the entities to getting inside him.  I don't want to scare you, but I have never, in all my years of doing this, experienced anything as terrifying as their presence", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "There is something we could try. A way of calling him back. I would need your complete trust", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "No. No. This has gone too far", "docId": "Insidious.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I have given her a chance, and I did that because I wanted to help you. But I cannot have somebody telling us that the reason our son is in a coma is because his soul is floating off somewhere in another dimension", "qsentId": 42}]